KEIICHI KATSUNO

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER



PROFILE

A Ruby on Rails developer based in Melbourne.

My career progression has zigzagged for the past 8 years in various industries and countries, started with Sales and Marketing in manufacturing equipment and machinery in Japan, turned into Production in coffee in The UK and Colombia, and finally, ended up in Software Engineering for the sports industry in Australia, which currently I am obsessed with. These journeys have always been growing my confidence to survive in this competitive world and let me deeply understand what I want to achieve in my career.

Currently, I am pursuing growing my skillset in backend and frontend web application development, enjoying committing to production as a software developer at Stack Team App.

EXPERIENCE

- AUSTRALIA

Full-stack Web Application Developer - Part Time

Jun 2021 - Present

- at Team App, Melbourne

Engaging in web application development by using Ruby on Rails and Vue.js.

Production Coffee Roaster - Full-Time

Oct 2020 - Jun 2021

- at Small Batch Roasting Co., Melbourne

Joined as a production coffee roaster at a high-quality coffee wholesaler in Melbourne. Responsible for product development. Found my passion in pursuing product quality to improve user experience and its demand.

- COLOMBIA

Production Quality Inspector - Internship

Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

- at InverCafé Ltda, Chinchiná, Caldas, Colombia

Joined as a quality control assistant at a high-quality green coffee producer/exporter in Colombia. Acquired an intricate knowledge of the industry. Realised that the industry is still slow to adopt technological change globally, which gradually made me get interested in software development.

- THE UK

Production Roaster - Full-Time - at The Roasting Shed Co, London, Endland

Jan 2018 - Sep 2019

Turned my career into a production coffee roaster at a small coffee wholesaler in the UK. Engaging in the local coffee market while building fundamental knowledge and skillsets of product development.

- JAPAN

Sales Development Representative - Full-Time

Apr 2013 - July 2017

- at Yuasa Trading Co, Fukuoka / Osaka, Japan

Started my career in Sales and Marketing of industrial machinery and equipment at one of the leading trading companies in Japan. Enjoyed building the relationship with stakeholders and gained strong confidence to work in a team.

- Doubling my area sales within a 12-month period. (Both sales figure and profit)
- Successful relationship development with stakeholders, while ensuring developing sales figures.
- Accurate day to day order management in the fast-paced trade environment.

EDUCATION

Master of Information Technology.

Jul 2021 - Jul 2023

- at RMIT University, Melbourne, Australia

Majoring in computer science to gain more intricate knowledge and skill set in backend web application development. Becoming a skilled back-end web developer is my current objective.

Software Development - Computer Science

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

- at Le Wagon, Melbourne, Australia

Acquired fundamental skills of web application development in Ruby on Rails within a 9-weeks intensive coding bootcamp.

Bachelor of Business Administration

Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

- at KinDai University, Osaka, Japan

Built the ability of team management and individual collaboration in a team through engaging in the university's American Football club for four years while successfully studying business administration.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Ruby / Ruby on Rails
- HTML / CSS
- Javascript
- Vue.js
- jQuery
- ¡Builder

- Python
- Java
- Git / Git Hub
- Heroku
- AWS
- Docker

REFFERENCES

Andrew Kelly

Operator of Small Batch Roasting Co. 0404 817 517

Paal Ringstad

Operator of Le Wagon Melbourne 042 396 7255



